[
  {
      "Options": [
          "Are easily magnetized",
          "Create the magnetic force between two poles",
          "Create opposition to the passage of flux lines",
          "Focus lines of flux"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945550",
      "Question": "Ferromagnetic materials are materials that _____.",
      "Answer": "Are easily magnetized",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Flux lines; poles",
          "Electrostatic fields, quantum fields",
          "Magnetic fields; quantum",
          "Electrostatic fields; magnetic fields"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945551",
      "Question": "Electromagnetic fields are formed by combining _____ and _____.",
      "Answer": "Electrostatic fields; magnetic fields",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "The magnetic force between two poles.",
          "The non-rotating electrical parts of generator or motor",
          "A device that converts mechanical energy into electrical energy",
          "Any material that is easily magnetized, like nickel, cobalt, and iron"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945552",
      "Question": "What is a stator?",
      "Answer": "A device that converts mechanical energy into electrical energy",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Number of loops; watts",
          "Resistance; voltage",
          "Number of loops; voltage",
          "Resistance; watts"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945553",
      "Question": "Increasing the _____ in the wire that cuts a magnetic field will also increase the magnitude of _____ produced by electromagnetic induction.",
      "Answer": "Number of loops; voltage",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Increasing the number of loops in a coil",
          "Wrapping the windings of a conductor closer together",
          "Answers A and B",
          "None of the above"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945554",
      "Question": "What would create a stronger magnetic field?",
      "Answer": "C. Answers A and B",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Decrease",
          "Increase",
          "Do nothing to",
          "Minimize"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945558",
      "Question": "Increasing the current flowing through a conductor will _____ the strength f the electromagnetic field in that conductor.",
      "Answer": "Increase",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Power",
          "Current",
          "Wattage",
          "Voltage"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945559",
      "Question": "What can be increased in a DC generator by increasing the speed of the wire?",
      "Answer": "Voltage",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "voltage drop of American conductors to and from the load",
          "length of American conductors",
          "cross-sectional area of American conductors",
          "resistance of wire"
      ],
      "_id": "5db10459d5d1f127c9e0fbfb",
      "Question": "Circular mils are the units used to measure the ____.",
      "Answer": "cross-sectional area of American conductors",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Current flow",
          "Load value",
          "Area of wires or conductors",
          "Resistance of a wire or conductor"
      ],
      "_id": "5db10459d5d1f127c9e0fbfc",
      "Question": "What does the formula R=(KÃ—L)/A calculate?",
      "Answer": "Resistance of a wire or conductor",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "power",
          "current",
          "resistance",
          "voltage"
      ],
      "_id": "5db10459d5d1f127c9e0fbfe",
      "Question": "Lamps with the same value of resistance can have different wattage ratings if the _______ ratings are different.",
      "Answer": "voltage",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "always provides more than one possible path for the current to flow from the source and back",
          "allows the current to take a shorter path back to the source, avoiding the opposition of the load",
          "allows the current to flow to the intended destination through the load and back to the source",
          "is a circuit that has no current flowing through it"
      ],
      "_id": "5db10459d5d1f127c9e0fbff",
      "Question": "An open circuit _______.",
      "Answer": "is a circuit that has no current flowing through it",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Magnetic field flux; current flow; thrust",
          "Current flow; thrust; magnetic field flux",
          "Thrust; magnetic field flux; current flow",
          "Thrust; current flow; magnetic field flux"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945556",
      "Question": "When applying the Left-Hand Rule for Conductors, the thumb points in the direction of _____, the first and/or index fingers points in the direction of _____, and the center finger points in the direction of _____.",
      "Answer": "Thrust; magnetic field flux; current flow",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Inducing a wattage into a conductor by passing it through an electrostatic field",
          "Inducing a voltage into a conductor by passing it through a magnetic field",
          "Inducing an amp into a conductor by passing it through a magnetic field",
          "Inducing a shock into a conductor by passing it through magnetic field"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945557",
      "Question": "What is electromagnetic induction?",
      "Answer": "Inducing a voltage into a conductor by passing it through a magnetic field",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Conductor; magnetic field",
          "Magnetic field; flux lines",
          "Conductor; commutator",
          "Magnetic field; power source"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945561",
      "Question": "Relative motion between the _____ and _____ is needed to have a voltage induced.",
      "Answer": "Conductor; magnetic field",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Electrical generator",
          "Solar panel",
          "Hydraulic generator",
          "Conductor"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945562",
      "Question": "What device converts mechanical energy into electrical energy?",
      "Answer": "Electrical generator",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Electrostatic and magnetic fields combine",
          "Like poles repel each other and unlike poles attract each other",
          "There is opposition to the passage of flux lines",
          "Current flows through a conductor"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945565",
      "Question": "A magnetic field of concentric circles expanding perpendicular and outward from the conductor occurs when _____.",
      "Answer": "Current flows through a conductor",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Direction of flux lines",
          "Strength of the electromagnetic field",
          "Amount of resistance in the conductors",
          "Speed of the current flow"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945566",
      "Question": "If the direction of the current flow in a conductor is known, what can be determined by using the left-hand rule for conductors?",
      "Answer": "Direction of flux lines",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Slip rings",
          "Stators",
          "Coils",
          "Wires"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945570",
      "Question": "In DC Generators, a commutator is used instead of _____.",
      "Answer": "Slip rings",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Thumb",
          "Middle/center finger",
          "Index finger",
          "Pinky finger"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945571",
      "Question": "Using the Left-Hand Rule for generators, the _____ indicates the direction of the current induced into the armature.",
      "Answer": "Middle/center finger",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "The amount of resistance in conductors",
          "The motion, direction of magnetic field, and direction of current flow for three-pole switches",
          "The power, wattage, and voltage produced by a circuit",
          "The motion, direction of magnetic field, and the direction of the current flow for electromagnetic function"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d533",
      "Question": "In DC Theory, what does the Left-Hand Rule for generators show?",
      "Answer": "The motion, direction of magnetic field, and the direction of the current flow for electromagnetic function",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Positive charges",
          "Attraction or repulsion",
          "Negative charges",
          "Increased pole strength"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d536",
      "Question": "The magnetic lines of force flowing into and out of magnets causes magnets held to close to each other to have _____.",
      "Answer": "Attraction or repulsion",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Magnetic field of the circuit; magnetic force between the poles",
          "Magnetic field of the magnet; flux lines of the magnet",
          "Magnetic field of the electrons; magnetic line of force",
          "Magnetic field of the magnet; magnetic field of the electrons"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d539",
      "Question": "A voltage would be induced if there was a motion of electrons in a conductor caused by an interaction between the _____ and ______.",
      "Answer": "Magnetic field of the magnet; magnetic field of the electrons",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "The direction of the conductor passing through the flux lines",
          "The amount of resistance in the circuit",
          "The amount of voltage at the source",
          "The magnetic field of the electrons"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d53d",
      "Question": "If the direction of the current flow changes, what else will change?",
      "Answer": "The direction of the conductor passing through the flux lines",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Motion of electrons in a conductor caused by the interaction between the magnetic fields of the magnet and electrons",
          "Opposition to the passage of flux lines",
          "Attraction or repulsion that occurs when magnets are held close to each other",
          "Magnetic force between two poles"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d53a",
      "Question": "Reluctance is the _____.",
      "Answer": "Opposition to the passage of flux lines",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "always provides more than one possible path for the current to flow from the source and back",
          "allows the current to take a shorter path back to the source, avoiding the opposition of the load",
          "allows the current to flow to the intended destination through the load and back to the source",
          "is a circuit that has no current flowing through it"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d547",
      "Question": "A short circuit _______.",
      "Answer": "allows the current to take a shorter path back to the source, avoiding the opposition of the load",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Unlike; like",
          "Like; unlike",
          "North; south",
          "South; north"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a945568",
      "Question": "The _____ poles of magnets attract while _____ poles repel.",
      "Answer": "Unlike; like",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "Opposition to the passage of flux lines",
          "Magnetic force between two poles",
          "Ability of material to focus lines of flux",
          "Attraction or repulsion that occurs when magnets are held close to each other"
      ],
      "_id": "5db1053f628e9d2a0966d53f",
      "Question": "Permeability is the _____.",
      "Answer": "Ability of material to focus lines of flux",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "North; north",
          "South; north",
          "North; south",
          "South; south"
      ],
      "_id": "5d9a6c01475e0d068a949870",
      "Question": "The flux lines of a magnet leave the _____ end and enter the _____ end",
      "Answer": "North; south",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  },
  {
      "Options": [
          "lower; higher",
          "higher; lower",
          "higher; higher",
          "lower; lower"
      ],
      "_id": "5db104c0628e9d2a0966d51e",
      "Question": "The ____ a lampâ€™s resistance, the ____ a lampâ€™s wattage.",
      "Answer": "higher; lower",
      "__v": 0,
      "Attempted": false,
      "Correct": null
  }
]